Guide to the School of Nutrition records, 1942-1979.
School of Nutrition records, 1942-1979.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
School of Nutrition records, 1942-1979.
23-15-2781
Cornell University.School of Nutrition.
.4 cubic ft.
Minutes, lists, proposals, programs, and other records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes of meetings of the Faculty, lists of graduates, proposals, programs, and other records of the School.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
On March 14, 1974 the Board of Trustees voted to abolish the Graduate School of Nutrition and the Department of Human Nutrition and Food in the College of Human Ecology and to establish the Division of Nutritional Sciences, an intercollege unit within the Colleges of Agriculture and Life Sciences and Human Ecology.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes of meetings of the Faculty, lists of graduates, proposals, programs, and other records of the School.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.School of Nutrition.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University--Graduate School of Nutrition.
Subjects:
Nutrition--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Policy Committee Meetings, 1949-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- School of Nutrition-Reports and Memos, 1940s (Box 1, Folder 2)
- School of Nutrition Bylaws, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- School of Nutrition-Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1942-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- School of Nutrition-Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1952-1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- School of Nutrition-Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Graduates, Lists by Years, 1947-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Graduate School Candidates, 1952-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Proposal to Graduate School, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Proposal - Addition to School of Nutrition, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Early Years of the Graduate School of Nutrition-by Leonard Maynard, 1941-1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - Annual Report, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - Annual Report, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - Annual Report, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - Annual Report, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - Annual Report, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Graduate School of Nutrition Faculty, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Brochures and Booklets produced by the Graduate School of Nutrition, 1950s (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Information about the International Nutrition Program, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Article about Graduate School of Nutrition, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Richard Barnes, Director of the School of Nutrition - Vitae, Publications, Lectures, 1958-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Memo to Faculty from Dean Knapp about Reorganization of Nutrition into a School of Nutrition, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)